<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contract>

    <title>
        <text>Sample of the five elements at level 1</text>
    </title>

    <subtitle>This file is to test : - title - sub-title - contract-front -
        date-block - parties - party - body - back -
        attachments - attachment
    </subtitle>

    <body>

        <title>Interpretations</title>

        <item-with-children marker-type="disc">
            <item>In these Articles:</item>

            <child-item>
                <item>**“Address”** means a postal address or, for the purposes of electronic communication, a
                    fax number, email address or telephone number for receiving text messages;</item>
            </child-item>

            <child-item>
                <item>
                    **“Articles”** means the Company’s articles of association;
                </item>
            </child-item>
        </item-with-children>

        <item>
            Unless the context requires otherwise, other words or expressions contained in these Articles bear
            the same meaning as in the Companies Act 2006 as in force on the date when these Articles become
            binding on the Co-operative.
            Schedule 1 to the Companies (Model Articles) Regulations 2008 shall apply to the Co-operative, save
            where amended or replaced by these Articles.
            In the case of any variation or inconsistency between these Articles and the model articles, these
            Articles shall prevail.
        </item>

        <title>Offer of shares and debentures</title>

        <item>
            The Co-operative is a private company and accordingly shall not offer to the public any type of shares
            in or debentures of the Co-operative nor shall it allot or agree to allot such shares or debentures
            with a view to their being offered for sale to the public.
        </item>

        <title>Purpose</title>

        <item>
            The purpose of the Co-operative is to carry out its function as a co-operative and to abide by the
            internationally recognised co-operative values and Co-operative Principles as defined by the International
            Co-operative Alliance. This article is Entrenched in accordance with section 22 of the Act; any
            alteration to this article requires the approval of 100% of the Members.
        </item>

        <!-- Do not include the following if the Co-operative wishes to have unrestricted objects and may carry out any lawful activity.   -->

        <title>OBJECTS</title>

        <item>
            The objects of the Co-operative are specifically restricted to carry on the business as a co-operative……
        </item>

        <title>POWERS</title>

        <item>
            To further its objects the Co-operative may do all such lawful things as may further the Co-operative's objects and,
            in particular, may borrow or raise funds for any purpose.
        </item>

        <title>MEMBERSHIP</title>

        <item>
            The first Members of the Co-operative will be the subscribers to the memorandum of association of the
            Co-operative. Only Employees may be Members of the Co-operative.
        </item>

        <item-with-children marker-type="loweralpha">
            <item>All Employees on taking up employment with the Co-operative may be admitted to membership of the Co-operative,
                    except that the Co-operative in a general meeting may by a majority vote decide to exclude from membership:</item>

            <child-item>
                <item>Newly appointed Employees during such reasonable probationary period as may be specified
                            in their terms and conditions of employment;</item>
            </child-item>

            <child-item>
                <item>
                    Employees working less than a prescribed number of hours per week (or per month); provided
                            that any such criteria for exclusion is applied equally to all Employees.
                </item>
            </child-item>
        </item-with-children>

        <item>
            In accordance with the Co-operative Principle of voluntary and open membership, whilst the Co-operative shall
            undertake to encourage its Employees to become Members, membership must be voluntary and as a result cannot
            be a condition of employment.
        </item>


    </body>


</contract>